Alexis Y Sanabria

Full Stack Developer

Full Stack Web Developer able to build a sophisticated web application with a full database backend all the way from mockup to rollout. Adept at working with diverse teams to implement projects. Also experienced in all project phases using Agile Methodologies. Extremely punctual, responsible, reliable, hard worker, quick learner and very well organized.

EXPERIENCE

Elite Digital - (Lead Full stack Developer) Toronto,, ON Dec 2021 - June 2024

Successfully led and contributed to multiple projects, overseeing their creation and ongoing maintenance. Developed project plans, allocated resources, and ensured timely completion. Collaborated with cross-functional teams to enhance project functionality and user experience. Implemented effective problem-solving strategies to address project challenges and issues.

Isara (Through Aerotek/AcTalent) - (Full stack Developer Remo Waterloo, ON Ian 2021 - Dec 2021

- Collaborated to the Advance Project by coding, debugging, and testing the back-end and front-end, within a team of 30 other developers/testers.
- Provided code reviews to other team members branches before merging them with the base code.

Amazing Pet Grooming - (Graphic Designer / Web Developer) Milton, ON 2016 - 2020

- Designed and developed compelling logos, flyers, and additional marketing materials.
- Designed a Full-stack-app to improve the way of handling clients and employees schedule
- Solved customer issues / IT related issues on a daily basis.

PRIVATE PROJECT COLLABORATION

Isara Advance Crypto Agility Suite Cryptographic management platform:

https://www.isara.com/products/isara-advance-crypto-aa ility-suite.html Enterprise solution for managing, discovering, and remediating cryptographic infrastructures within organizations.

905-299-2366

alexisyep@gmail.com

Portfolio:https://www.alexisysanabria.com LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexis-san

abria-80002574/

Github: https://github.com/alexisyepes

Cambridge, ON N1T-118

BUILT PROJECTS

Web Application Full Management System for a Small business.

https://www.amazingpetgrooming.ca/

This React/Node Application was built for a Pet Grooming business. The admin of the page is able to add employees into the system, so they can login to the private pages based on their roles, where they can manage the clients' database, add appointments to their own Calendars and adjust their working hours. Customers are also able to book appointments online. This Application solved several issues this business faced in the past.

SKILLS

FRONT-END	BACK-END
React	NodeJs
Typescript	Express
Next Js	MySQL
Javascript	PostgreSQL
HTML	MongoDB
CSS/SASS	FaunaDB
CSS Modules	Sanity
Bootstrap	GraphQL
JQuery	Solr
Handlebars	NodeMailer
Rest API	Postmark
Apollo Client	Sendgrid
Firebase	Jwt Authentication
Cl ·C / I · · · l	D . I

on Shopify / Liquid Passport Is

Cypress Testing

MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

React Native

OTHER TECHNOLOGIES / SKILLS

VS Code GitHub / GitLab Git Version Control Git Bash **MVC Pattern**

Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects

Bilingual: Spanish/English

EDUCATION

University of Toronto, Toronto, ON Full-stack Web **Development Bootcamp** 2018-2019 An intensive bootcamp, dedicated to designing and building full stack web applications. Compu-Ingenieros,

Bogota, COL Computer Programming Program

2002-2003 Two year program dedicated to computer programming fundamentals using Visual Basic, as well as computer maintenance, and graphic design: Photoshop/Illustrator.